Next up, we have the National Weather Forecast.
Motoko.
Don't you have a study session planned with your friends?
It's not until later.
Okay.
Somebody I didn't know called yesterday.
Huh?
Yeah, like called on the phone.
Was a boy.
Said his name was Kitahata and asked for Yuta.
But that's a little confusing when you call this specific household.
Since all of us answer to Yuta.
Right.
But...
Once you figured out it was for me, then what'd you do?
I hung up on the guy.
Please turn the volume down.
What gives? That is so rude!
When the call isn't for you, pass the phone!
You! Pass the phone!
You were in the bath at the time anyway.
And went to bed early.
So what's the deal?
Are you crushing on this kid?
You don't even know him, okay?
And you have no business asking me that!
He'd better not be a womanizer.
Don't dare bring him home when I'm not here to be your personal bodyguard.
I would never!
Kitahata has his own crush and the whole school knows!
It's like way obvious!
We walk home from school together everyday like they do, how could it not be?
But their relationship hasn't developed beyond a one-sided infatuation because the girl he likes has already got a boyfriend!
So, it's not like Kitahara could...
Hmm?
Are you done freaking out?
Yeah, guess I am.
Really wish I could solve the mystery behind why he called.
I can help you there.
You said today's study session will be canceled if it's not...
Then just say so to begin with, idiot!
Thank you.
I'm pretty sure you said you'll be coming home late today, right?
My friend is coming over, so things might get a little loud.
Take your time and be safe.
wobbling.
them barking.
Sorry.
food is on the Novinc話 Treatment Play.
Tee.
Check.
Snacks.
Now all that's left to do is wait.
Yuta, do you have plans this afternoon?
No.
I'm free.
I heard you're applying to the same high school.
So, want to study together?
They say teaching each other's a great way to learn.
Yeah, sure.
Absolutely.
Okay, cool.
I'll drop my stuff up at home and head over to your place.
We're doing exciting together, so stop reading into things aren't even there, stupid rape!
Please, um, come on in and warm up, Kitahara.
Ki-ta-ha-da!
Let's go again!
You told me you were gonna be late, but you came straight home!
I don't remember saying a single word about being late today.
Just like I don't remember you saying anything about Kitahara coming over!
Grandpa, I'm borrowing your model sword!
What? The replica?
He was kidding, Grandpa! We're just friends, having a study session!
So, what time's he getting here? Pretty soon?
Well, he said he'd come once he dropped some stuff off at home.
Hmm...
Study in the living room.
No telling what the average middle schooler gets up to these days.
Should I call the cops in advance?
Will you stop acting like we live in some dangerous part of town
surrounded by delinquents and go find a girlfriend to occupy your kooky thoughts?
You wouldn't come home early if your love life wasn't dead!
I'd rather spend my time with a girlfriend, too.
There's no pain like being the single ostrich in a flock of lovebirds.
Well, anywho, I can brew you a nice pot of tea if you want.
All I want you to do is buzz off!
Hmm? Is she not home?
Uh...
Yuda?
Keep out! I mean it!
Step one foot in there and I'll run away from home!
Stay in your room!
My presence shouldn't even matter if you're not up to anything!
So save it! You're just disappointing me!
Don't play the concerned loving brother card while you're holding me at sword point!
Want me to drop my sword? Then you drop yours first! Deal!
Sorry to interrupt.
Um, hi...
You're the guy?
Uh...
Hey! He's our guest!
I take it you're...
Her...
Brother?
That's correct!
Come in.
We have tea.
But that's all.
Would you stop being a jerk?!
You can feel free to ignore him.
He's just in a majorly bad mood right now.
So...
Cool!
Kitahara?
Hello?
Oh, uh...
Did you say something, Yuda?
Best brace yourself. Our tea's bitter.
I prefer a sharper taste.
The tea's not all that's bitter.
Well, look who decided to come back.
You want some tea?
It's the only drink we have to offer.
Tea's one of my favorites!
It's even more bitter than it was before.
Challenge accepted!
Fine. I'll go get that started.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
Seems he's always cranky when you're here.
No, really, it's fine.
I'm the one who's imposing, after all.
What's the age gap between the two of you?
Three years.
He's a senior in high school.
A senior, huh?
There, tea is served.
Can you set it down without trying to break it?!
Um...
Thanks for the hospitality.
Excuse me!
What are you settling in for?!
Go read somewhere else!
No need to get worked up.
I don't mind.
Am I getting in the way?
Of course you aren't, sir!
There you have it, little sis.
He just said that out of politeness!
Pretty sure it was out of honesty.
Right, Kippahara?
Quit acting frankly!
Um...
I'm so sorry for the way my brother's behaving.
He's typically on the quiet side and less obnoxious.
Uh...
I was only half listening to you.
Could you, um...
Repeat that?
Mm-hmm.
Don't come in again!
Komoto...
That's a shared living space, you know.
The stakes!
I thought I understood Kitahara, but now I'm not so sure.
It's one puzzle I can't solve either.
Like, I would even argue that I'm more confused than you are.
How can you sit there and claim you're confused when you're the whole root of the issue?!
Are you really so oblivious you can't see that all of this is your fault?!
Huh?!
You're pinning this on me?!
Got some seaweed in your brain?!
You're the blackhead who won't acknowledge your past actions, you LG ball!
What?!
LG ball?!
Give me back the Kitahara, Yusuno!
I...
I'm sorry?
Talk to me, sis.
Do you not like the kid anymore?
It would be easier if that were true.
He and I are still friends, so we chat pretty much on a daily basis.
But...
It's like he loses interest when we talk.
He's after something else.
Oh...
Such sad eyes.
Guys!
I get the feeling he's just using me as a stand-in for you, because we look so much alike!
Is he seriously straight so far in your mind?!
Shut up!
This wouldn't be half a bet if I'd been born cuter, but instead I'm the misfortune of looking like you're easily unattractive-
Do you think that bet had apologized to Mom right now?!
Also, take a look in the mirror, because we're very attractive!
At school, I'm constantly getting told how cute I am!
Liar!
Then you should have a harem of girlfriends, but you don't even have one!
Who said anything about a harem?!
What kind of question is that?
Most guys say, what's up, when they bump into a bro, but I get, am I cute?
You hit your head.
Not lately, no.
Skeptical?
It's not about me.
Motoko doesn't think she's cute because of how identical we are.
What?!
Your sister's pure adorable!
I'm feeling better already!
Thank you, Hori!
I was complimenting her, not you.
What about a longer hairstyle?
For me?
Dude, no.
Your sister.
New Doom might bring out her confidence.
Uh, her hair gets real unruly, so she refuses to grow it out.
Well, her shorter hairstyle's totally cute, if you ask me.
You wouldn't be talking about me, would you?
Or me?
That's sure a confident grin, considering I said her.
Uh, I guess hair's a sensitive subject, huh?
And while she does resemble you, your sister's cuter, hands down.
Am I ugly?
Motoko's the focus right now, not you.
Well, it's probably just a puberty thing.
You should enjoy the time she has before she's in heat.
I hope you're not suggesting my sister is a dog.
Yeah, um, humans don't go into heat, dude.
I aced health class, um, makes sense.
We probably wouldn't have that declining birth rate dilemma if we did.
This is a dumb conversation.
Yo, I'm going through puberty as we speak!
If you were actually going through puberty, you wouldn't probably declare it to the world!
Then you'll be in heat before you know it, Yoshikawa.
Which is fine by me!
I'm starting to wonder if puberty's responsible for the weird stuff Motoko's been saying.
Define weird.
She told me to stop flirting and just hook up with Sengoku.
And every time she hears me get a message from you or Miyamura, she asks, is it from a girl?
Uh, sounds like she doesn't realize Sengoku's a guy.
Or she might just be messing with you.
It's possible.
I think Ayasaki is more attractive than Sengoku, though.
Yeah, from what I know about you, he would.
You know, speaking of love interest, her crush was all Motoko could talk about when she came over.
So if she's feeling unpretty, it could just be... misplaced frustration?
It's funny you mention her crush. Because the person Motoko likes appears to like me.
So, Motoko bats for the ladies?
No, that's not it.
Does this diagram explain it? It seems kinda hard to believe.
Yep, that about sums it up. It is hard to believe.
I feel sorry for Motoko.
Not me?
She'll never be able to rest in peace.
Please don't kill off my sister, okay, Hori? And it's not like I stole him!
Sorry, but that qualifies as theft in my book.
I wanted nothing to do with this relationship from the get-go, I swear!
I'm a 24-7 ladies man!
That sentence out of context would get you in a different kind of trouble.
And before we forget, wanna share how you feel about the Prez?
Not sure why this is a misunderstanding, but if you must know, I clearly like Sengoku!
Uh, hey Prez!
So Yorta likes both ladies and Sengoku?
Oh wow, this is getting so complex. Just drama, drama, drama!
It is not! You're the only ones making it complex!
My apologies.
Stop, Sengoku.
You wound me.
Get a girlfriend and all misunderstandings go away.
Sure. I'll go and get one from the store.
Is a woman made entirely out of plastic able to love me?
Is there an actual person you're into?
Someone in your class you see every day!
Nah, not now at least.
He almost seems normal for once.
Um, I'm lost.
Same.
You feeling sick?
Or just feel like skipping school?
Oh!
For the record, I came in and tried to wake you up once before.
Did you really?
Was I simply dead to the world?
You said I know and pulled the covers right back over your head.
That means I didn't get the memo!
Um, you gonna eat some breakfast?
And wind up later than I already am?
You need to eat at least a slice of toast. Mom's orders.
I'll dine and dance.
You should be making your way to school, too.
I will.
And have a good day!
It's my first time seeing someone actually run to school with toast in their mouth.
Sprinting, while eating bread, dries out your mouth like crazy!
I can't eat and run at the same time!
Walking it is.
I'm late! I'm late!
I just experienced the bump into a boy with toast in your mouth trope, so there's a decent chance he's a super hot transfer student!
Hey, Yoshikawa? You know that I can hear you, right? I being Yuta?
Fancy running into you here. Good morning.
Is it, though?
I take it you'll reflect, too?
Uh-huh. I should've gotten a bit way earlier.
That we'd make it even if we ran, so let's just walk.
I'm late! I'm late!
What? Are you guys on a stroll? You're both as late as I am!
It says you with your Onigiri.
I woefully realize we'll be late no matter what.
No, I'm woeful, too.
Flavor?
It only has salt.
Sad?
I'm late! I'm late!
What are the three of you doing? We all need to hurry!
Then why do you stop at the store?
Flavor?
It's a meat bun.
All of you yelled about being late as if shouting it would up your speed.
True.
Is there morning assembly today?
Nope.
Let's take our time, then.
Huh?
Oh, hey. You're here bright and early. Good morning.
What?
I can't believe what I'm seeing!
The Sengoku is late? That never happens!
Um...
We third years only have classes in the afternoon today.
I'm early on account of student council matters.
Huh?
Oh, I think I remember hearing that in homeroom yesterday. Oops.
I would have slathered my toast and jam if I had known!
What wavelength are the four of you on?
I don't know, man. I just wish I could have put something in my rice ball!
Oh, Shiso leaves! Rez gets it!
Uh... Shiso leaves?
Those middle schoolers?
You guys thought that you were late only to show up the earliest of all?
You dummies!
Hey, together we dumb, divided we fall.
They gave us the morning off because prospective students were coming to get a look at the place.
Ah! Those kids I saw were middle schoolers then!
Yep, they were.
Where's Yuki? And Miyamura?
They left a minute ago to buy some drinks.
What I want to know is why you're here early.
Oh, it's silly.
Kyan Kyan!
Hey!
Ready to hit the school store?
Let's do it.
Since it's a ghost town, there won't be any lumpings.
Want to follow their lead and snack some lunch?
Yeah!
There are more middle schoolers down there.
Wonder if there's a lot or just a few.
I have no idea.
My head's too busy reeling because they all look so young.
Is your sister coming?
There isn't a snowball's chance in hell.
Motoko hates doing stuff with groups.
If she tours this place, she's on her...
So, while I'm not positive, I'm pretty sure that we're somewhere around here.
Hey, Tom!
What's up, Ju?
Go!
Disappear, body!
Are you in pain or something?
Um, excuse me.
We got a little lost.
You know the place you're trying to go?
The edge of this field.
We're supposed to meet up with the rest of our class there.
Oh, you'll get there quicker through the exit on the side of the building.
Follow this hallway until you reach the staircase on the right.
The doors at the bottom lead outside.
Great.
Thanks so much.
Shu, get over here!
I got my name!
I don't understand!
Man, what's with him?
Well, um, we should get going.
Right.
Take care and whatnot.
Yes, please leave.
Do I wanna know?
Stop goofing off and let's get to the cafeteria, okay?
We gotta beat the lunch crowd while we still have a chance, Iyura!
Ayasaki, no!
Iyura!
Come on!
Did you see something?
What happened?
components, the one time a girl calls my name!
Hyuura!
Oh, itero!
Hello?
Use me to해요!
Kitahara's still close!
ポлат me for sure!
Sorry ladies!
Go on without me!
Stop holding up that wall and move.
Oh.
Right.
Right. I'm sorry.
Wait.
Is that you?
Senpai?
I'm Senpai now?
If he'd called me anything else,
I could have played it off like he had the wrong guy!
Senpai, um...
Oh, it's hard to pretend I'm a total stranger when he calls me that!
Just scram, kid!
What are you still doing up here?
You're supposed to be outside, so hurry up and get going!
Don't bully the middle schoolers!
Look, the poor kid's shaking from head to toe.
I think they're more afraid of you and your lethal surprise attacks, Yasuda.
So how do you know Iorta?
Do you go to the same middle school that he did?
Sorry, but do either of you know if my Senpai has a girlfriend?
I get stifled giggles and sympathy?
What do we do?
Should we just lie and say that he does?
I'm thinking we dodged the question altogether.
Now I feel even worse!
That's enough questions out of you for one day,
so time to say goodbye!
Uh?
Wanna tag along with us to the school store?
No!
We have to go back to our school for lunch, but thank you.
Oh.
Huh.
Was that a sigh of relief?
This kid just needs to leave.
Please trust me out!
Okay, okay, okay.
Beat it if you got somewhere to be, guys.
And since you all are having navigation issues, I'll act as your personal guide.
I appreciate it?
What the heck?
Be nice to your actual students, too.
Why would I do that?
I can't recall you ever being nice to me.
Huh?
Yasuda.
I think.
Wow.
Somebody who looks up to Yuda?
I would've left to see that.
Can't deny I would've, too.
Why?
It was boring.
Nothing at all worth seeing.
Remy has to disagree.
Seeing you get flustered every time he called you senpai was so worth it.
That's a normal reaction to have.
Perfectly normal.
What isn't normal is how averse you were to simply being around this kid.
Bad terms.
Can't be that bad considering how comfortable the kid was.
I didn't know he'd be here today, but he's one of my little sister's classmates.
Huh?
Then try and get along for her sake, yeah?
Oh, it's complicated, Hori.
What's the catch?
What am I missing here?
Stop being wishy-washy and just say it!
Is that kid possibly the one?
He is!
Isn't he?
I didn't see him!
Man, I missed out.
Shoo.
For real?
No joke.
Um, what do you mean by the one, Remy?
I'm lost.
Same.
둘
Oh, I'm lost.
I don't want to leave you alone
Ah, what are you doing today?
That's the day that I'm like
I'm looking forward to it
I'm saying that you need to be in front of me
Ah, I'm looking forward to it
また想いが張り裂けそうなのに
URLより短い言葉にしかできない私です
I'm so sad
どこでも君に飛べるように
出会えるようにできてたなら
このままポイ方として해주継承します
ご視聴ありがとうございました
私はこれにも